[Music]
Siri where are you going obviously I'm
heading to work you stupid [__] unlike
some ponies I don't have time to lie
around deadlines don't just meet
themselves you know oh I just thought
maybe we could cuddle a bit before
work yeah that's not happening Coco I've
got things to do ponies to impress you'd
understand if you had even a shred of
ambition oh wait I have a surprise for
you girl if you shat in my [__] bed
again oh Siri you're so funny you know
that was an accident now hop on up here
and open your gift already you bought me
a [__] present for our
anniversary what anniversary cocoa pom L
we met each other 8 days ago exactly
it's our 8 day
anniversary it better be a bag of adult
diapers I'm tired of your
leaking a fruit
dehydrator you always say how you love
dehydrating fruits when have I ever said
anything like that I don't don't even
know what to use this for turn $2 worth
of grapes into a box of 50 Cent raisins
we can make yummy treats like like
homemade banana
chips Coco sweetie I don't do homemade
anything okay I'm a special breed I get
all my fruits delivered like the
professionals but we can still it's
seems you're due for another reality
check so listen up this us what whatever
you're seeing it's not a thing us
spending time together like this
Strictly Business oh I know you might
not feel the same way now but maybe
someday you will this is why you'll
never make it in a Fashion World in this
career it's not about trivial things
such as feelings it's about who you know
and me I know ponies who matter and you
well lucky for you you know me
I'm off to the fashion show don't you
dare be
late hey bulk what's the matter did you
get stood up by your hearts and have
stay date again how lame I bet she ran
away because he got her a fruit
dehydrator or some [__] look he's hiding
the flowers behind his back that's so
funny oh well deviled eggs real romantic
pal maybe that's why you're all alone
yeah who would ever want to date a
stallion that eats deviled eggs oh look
he's crying what a big muscular
baby mommy I'm back from horse
school oh my little bulky WLKY what
happened to your eye did you get bullied
at school again today for being [__]
as [__] [__] yes oh my poor baby your
bulk eat some egg that should cheer you
up yay I love
eggs no pony [__] move this is a
robbery who the hell are you that's for
me to know and you do not so shut up
stay back Mommy I eat a lot of eggs I'll
protect you with my [__]
strength I will eat them because my
mommy told me to so I'll grow big and
strong to protect myself from bullying
like you hey you girls better leave him
alone look Carrot Top bulk got himself a
bodyguard you know you shouldn't just go
around making fun of ugly retards for no
reason especially on hars and H's day
that's so mean yeah and what are you
going to do about it [__] you can't
even drink a glass of water without
using two
hes yeah well I don't spill as much as I
used to
[Laughter]
hey Derpy is a good friend with big
slappable butt cheeks so you should
treat her with more respect whatever man
you two lamos have fun with your deviled
eggs I'm sorry bulk I wanted to stick up
for you since we often sat next to each
other when we got on the short bus to go
to school no thank you Derpy you stood
up for me when no pony else did here eat
this boiled egg it will make you feel
better I don't really like eggs eat
it you know Derpy I thought hearts and
Po's day was supposed to be about love
and friendship but now I know that it's
not it's not no it's about hate and
getting mad about those more fortunate
than
oneself um I don't think that's the
right lesson why would I care about what
you think you're [__] I'm going to
hunt those girls down and give them a
taste of a beef stew by farting in their
face so are you in or what okay I always
wanted to be an accomplice in
something there they are in the taco
Bale those [__] hores go inside and
beat them up me but I thought you were
going to do it I ain't going back to
jail did too much time already well me
too we'll just rock paper scissors for
It Rock Paper Scissors
Shoot ha when I got rock I got rock too
you [__] well I got hit first after
you hit them a few times feed them a
plate of
poop that was fast I tried bulk I really
did but when they started hitting me
with a really big burrito my options
became pretty limited don't worry my
friend I'm not disappointed in you just
myself for believing in you hey bulk
since it's obvious no pony wants to [__]
you do you want to hang out with me this
hearts and hoov's day instead no you are
an ugly horse as friends friends also
deserve to have fun on hearts and who's
day why we're not even friends we always
have fun together remember that one time
when you got beat up 45 seconds ago
that's the one good times look Derpy
I'll hang out with you because I got
nothing better to do but if I see a girl
with a big ass don't start crying if I
drop you like a sack of
beans [__]
[__] oh shiny I got you a little
something I know you said you didn't
want me to get anything for Hearts and
Hooves Day but I just couldn't help
myself you're always telling me how much
you love dehydrating fruits when have I
ever said anything like that what am I
supposed to use this for or turn $2
worth of grapes into a box of 50 Cent
raisins well excuse me for trying to get
you something useful at least I got you
something you didn't even bother to get
me anything think again
[__] oh joy another comically oversized
plastic comb shiny you get me this every
year how many of these Combs do you
think I actually need I don't know but
now you've got
six hey you with the ribbon are you
talking to me do you see any Pony else
around I am well I'm not talking to you
oh my gosh you're Princess Cadence of
the Crystal Empire yes it's really me
it's not every day you get to meet
royalty is it I'm like your biggest fan
you're kind and and your relationship
with Shining Armor is just perfect yes I
know meeting royalty is quite the
privilege isn't it Lulu pastel you
almost know my name that is such an
honor I know I am a gracious princess
aren't I now don't you think it's only
appropriate that you show the proper
amount of respect to an Alicorn
Princess yes your ladyship princess as
you know it's hearts and Hoops day would
you maybe want to see the gift I got for
my boss Siri no no thank you oh how
lovely a fruit
dehydrator no wonder you're spending
hearts and hoofs day sad and alone what
do you mean come on this is your boss
we're talking about you're not going to
win your boss over with some dumb
kitchen gadget go suck his balls Siri's
a girl I see so you a [__] Coco I
think what shining is trying to say is
that you should focus on getting her
something more meaningful a gift only
you can give to her that I thought this
was meaningful I even tested it at
Goodwill it's
functional [__] don't like kitchen
gadgets because it reminds them of their
place think about what she would truly
cherish maybe an experience you've
shared or something personal that only
you could give well I spilled coffee on
her favorite scarf she yelled at me for
10 minutes and then made me buy her a
new one she did call me incompetent but
her tone was really pretty now you're on
the right track but let's think of a
happier memory shall we
a happier memory H let me
[Music]
think welcome to Cocoa Palm El flower
Emporium you are very wet wow really I
had no idea anyway I ordered a bouquet
this morning is it done and what is what
is your name she's really pretty she
must be some kind of fashion model wow
just wow the one pony in this entire
city who doesn't know my name and of
course she's the one handling my order
the name sori Suri Paula May don't you
forget it again I think you made a
mistake Miss Paula your pickup date was
actually set for
tomorrow but I can totally make it for
you right now it won't take me too
long so miss poir what kind of flowers
do you want you'll find we have quite
the variety you're asking me shouldn't
you know what looks good you're supposed
to be the expert
[Music]
here are those safety scissors the other
employees don't trust me with anything
else I promise it won't take very long I
almost got through one stem quit horsing
around give them to me and I'll get it
done
myself I like you you do you seem
absolutely pathetic but in like a
weirdly cute way every pony around me is
either useless incompetent or both it's
exhausting being the only only one with
a brain you know that does sound
frustrating finally Somey gets it I
shouldn't have to walk into some sad
Little Flower Shop and beg for basic
service if I had an assistant this
wouldn't happen I hear what you're
saying great because I just decided
something like literally just now you're
going to be my
assistant you're what you're quiet and
clearly you know how to work with your
Hooves and you're way more interesting
than some dumb flowers so
congratulations you're
hired 19 years old 19 and a half I'll be
turning 20 next month is that so so
she's still
underage this fo isn't even old enough
to drink how boring is it even worth my
time bothering with her
what about you don't you know it's rude
to ask a lady her age oh sorry it's fine
if we're going to be work Partners I
might as well tell you anyway
32 you don't look that old at all yeah I
get that a lot this is a little
embarrassing I hope she doesn't feel
like she's treating a kid to dinner
maybe I shouldn't have ordered the
chicken nugget so what made you you
decide to get into fashion I didn't give
it much thought at all I chose this
career path because my family
recommended it they said it would be
easy for a young fashionista to find a
husband you're married that's nice as if
I have been at it for well over 10 years
all the good guys were taken while I was
busy stitching stupid
clothes so do you have any plans tonight
plans cancel them I'll make reservations
at a hotel tonight a hotel well I can't
bring a child drinking with me we'll
just have a little party of our
own oh my this room is
beautiful it's not the most expensive
but it's really high up it's amazing
I've never seen anything like this
before of course you haven't this hotel
room costs $8 whole dollars per
night come back Siri do I really belong
in a place like this you're so pathetic
it's adorable of course you don't do not
remove my
hand oh how hopelessly romantic Coco I
think the answer should be obvious you
should buy her flowers
flowers that's it a bouquet of beautiful
flowers to rekindle the Flames of
passion what a splendid idea princess no
it's a terrible idea flowers aren't
gifts they're food Shining Armor must
you truly put on the whole tough guy act
now look I'm just saying a daisy
sandwich shop is like two steps away
from a flower shop if we're going to do
this we're going to go big like my
balls oh shiny you're such a heartthrob
you really know how to make a girl's
spew like a geyser go on Lea get on in
there and rock her world what can go
wrong it's just Siri I've talked to her
a 100 times before yeah except this time
you're dressed as a [__]
[Music]
flower Miss sui I brought you a little
something and you'll be happy to know
it's not a fruit
dehydrator oh Coco you're back don't
mind me I just thought I'd relieve
myself before the fashion show but when
I came back to the room you were gone
hopefully throwing away that fruit
dehydrator I ran into these two sexy
[__] in the elevator I hope you won't
mind that I used some of the money out
of your paycheck these two hunks weren't
cheap wait Caroline my name is Coco and
stay out of my life will you you made me
look like like a complete
butt you're going to be my assistant
[Music]
[__] babe we just lost half of lost
Pegasus stay
down I said stay
down stop
it well they lover boy you think you can
take me an ex-military powerlifting
piece of [__] Twilight Sparkle may have
gotten the brains and the family but I
got the balls pull down your
pants oh
who the hell are you ponies assistant I
demand you call the police at once and
have these criminals hastily removed
your assistant left your ass you think
you can trample all over every Pony's
Hearts just because your man looks like
a couple of cinnamon rolls for some
reason my head does not look like
cinnamon rolls oh yes it does what's the
goal there are you just born looking
like breakfast why why are you like this
okay first of all lower your voice this
is my hotel room second of all why the
hey would you care Coco's my assistant
your assistant is a delicate flower
looking to be pollinated with love
listen pal I don't know what she told
you but I'm not a [__] [__] if she
gets her feelings hurt because I suck
balls that doesn't bother me one bit is
that how you truly feel or is it a mask
you put on because you're so chained up
in your own image to admit you've gone
past your Prime for some reason that
girl cares about you the way she talked
about you I figured there might be
something special too but from what I
see you're just another run-ofthe-mill
wash up so get lost before you end up
dragging that kid down with you shiny
we're done here let's go
find go go Power Ranger
[Music]
it hurts to be rejected doesn't
it there are so many ponies in this
world who don't
[Music]
care who will step on others just to
feel larger than
themselves oh great is the universe just
sending ponies to be awful to me tonight
now my Little Flower Pony I'm not here
to be awful towards you
I am only here because your heart is
suffering that's probably because my
heart is
breaking that's you a masterpiece of
heartbreak and I must admit I currently
have a particular interest in broken
things I feel so cold what's happening
to
me there it is such delicate sorrow the
essence of your heartbreak
and now it's mine give give it back give
me back my my
[Music]
heart so then he looks at me dead in the
eye and says bulk you [__] that wasn't
protein powder that was my grandma
sashes you drank his grandma I didn't
mean to who even takes their family's
cremated ashes to the gym anyway that's
crazy do you ever poop her
out oh my gosh a dead
Pony she's not dead she's breathing are
you sure because she looks super dead if
she was dead she wouldn't be breathing
unless she's a ghost hey if you're a
ghost say
something ow gentle you blueberry I
happen to be a very important Pony Siri
can you tell me what your relationship
with Coco is like she's an employee that
I hired and that's all I'm not abusing
her if that's what you're thinking I pay
her extremely well way more than she'd
ever get working at some other run of
the mil gig you know Coco says you're
the best boss she's ever had did she
my assistant what happened to her Somey
better start talking these two found her
laying in the street I think she's been
hit by a magical
curse oh fantastic are you saying she's
cursed to sleep on my couch forever this
is so inconvenient for me don't you
worry Miss Paula may I may not
personally know what kind of curse was
used on her but I think I know some pony
who might be able to help
us
H yes yes I see it's just as I initially
suspected this flower costume is
approximately four sizes to small the
seams around her cheeks are practically
bursting and about the curse oh yeah
it's definitely evil but I can't do
anything about that we're going to have
to call in a
professional
H yes yes I see
it's just as I thought this flower
costume is approximately four sizes to
small and about the curse oh yeah it's
definitely evil what kind of spell is it
I cannot say for Celestia forbids me
from sharing knowledge of evil magic but
you can figure out for yourself if
you're prepared to embark on the
challenge goodbye my friends but this
separation is not forever soon our
reunion shall be had when I gather even
greater knowledge
damn that portal was like a reverse fart
like they got pulled into a magic ass
hole Nightmare Moon where have you taken
me this is a far away place called The
Infinity
staircase at the very top of those
stairs situates a magical tone
containing every single evil spell
through all of existence including the
one that's been inflicted on your friend
Momo
caramel then that's where we'll find the
answer to Koko's curse easier said than
done do you know why it's called the
infinity stairs because it's infinite no
because it takes like two whole minutes
to climb which doesn't sound like much
but for horses that's practically
Infinity because climbing stairs is hard
for the untrained ones oh oh God no
exactly and there is no pony in all of
Equestria with an IQ over 40 some ponies
get halfway up and start thinking about
hay fries others remember that they
forgot to brush their Mane that morning
One Time air sat down on step
437 just three steps away from the top
to tie her horseshoes got bored and just
turned around and left I won't make the
same mistake as those who have faced
this trial
before we shall
see it's been two whole minutes I'm
starting to get worried they were so
young why did bad things happen to good
pones
we should have spent hearts and hoes day
at the club watching big titty [__]
do that lesbian [__] but instead I
killed my sister don't say that they're
dead [__] a pony who goes missing for a
couple of minutes in Equestria is as
good as dead I'm back every pony look
big bro this book is almost as big as me
Isn't that cool there it is the ancient
ritual that was used on Coco it's called
essence of the heart what's it do it
steals the the essence of one's heart
obviously but why for what purpose would
some want to steal Coco's heart the
means of the ritual is resurrection to
bring a dead Pony back to life what are
you
saying to finish the ritual the Caster
must gather three kinds of Hearts A
Broken Heart drenched in sorrow A Cruel
Heart full of malice angry and a pure
heart wholly Untouched by evil hooves
but then which one was our little Coco I
think we might already have an idea oh
please as if the two of you treated her
any better hey Derpy you were the one
who found her did you see who attacked
her no hey I got to go take a piss let
me know if you figure anything else out
while I'm going pee
PE yep just as I thought definitely a
top 10 piss might even make it to top
five if I really
commit enjoying the view back there you
purr you are going to be in so much
trouble when I'm done
[Music]
peeing that's what I thought [__] take
that godamn mask off you're going to
look me in my mangled eyes as I [__]
rape you
you are so lucky that I have no friends
because I would have so known who you
are right
[Music]
now oh my God she flushed herself down
the
toilet guys guys coc's attacker tried to
rape me and then she flushed herself
down the toilet did you get a good look
at her face yeah hurry and get me some
crayons
that's our little [__] everyone give
her a Round of Applause by tapping your
hose on the wood
floor
horse Derpy has failed us all I must
return to caner lot and inform my sister
of this dark force in the meantime I ask
that every pony here remain Vigilant we
do not know when this mysterious
attacker will strike again are we really
just going to leave her like this Coco
is not in immediate danger the attacker
already took what they wanted from her I
don't care about that who's going to
iron and steam my dresses I've got to
show to attend in 30
minutes that's sweet Coco is indeed
lucky to have some Pony who cares so
much can you imagine if the news got
word that an employee of mine died while
on the clock I'm simply covering my
bases huh
there's a Pony wearing a mask down there
and she's running
away that's her that's the lady who
attacked me in the bathroom come on bulk
we can't let her get
[Music]
away bulk we're going to lose her hurry
that fat ass
up I'm doing my best don't rush me oh my
gosh didn't your mommy ever teach you
how to fly why are you flying so slow my
mommy was murdered oh bulk when I was
just a cold 17 years ago from today a
burglar broke into my house and killed
my mother right in front of my very eyes
oh that was me I needed a couple bits to
buy a shamrock shake from McDonald's I
was going to tell you the next day at
school but since you were taking
steroids I was afraid you would beat me
up you killed my mom for a milkshake it
was only available for a limited
time I'm going to kill you
Derpy no get away from
me help me my wings aren't working oh
God save
me I am your God and you will die
knowing that God is a woman and a horse
and
[__] bulk bicep I didn't know you
that well but you were big and loud and
always flexing for some reason you kind
of looked like a marshmallow with hooks
honestly you probably should have taken
some flying lessons before trying to
chase a dangerous criminal but I guess
your heart was in the right place but
you know what you tried you gave it your
all even when your tiny pathetic wings
were flapping so hard they looked like
they were going to pop off your body you
kept going and then I murdered you see
you later
dude that was a beautiful speech Derpy
thank you do you want to come with me to
KFC and split a biscuit to honor bulk
how does that honor bulk I don't know
I'm just really hungry I'll have to
decline but thanks for the offer okay
I'll get two just in case you change
your mind this masked Pony she killed
two of our friends today she must be
stopped I completely agree little sis
but Cadence is over in that car waiting
to get [__] by me so we're going to
have to settle this another
day so uh I guess I'll be seeing you I
wish I could stay and help you protect
Coco purple ponies like us should stick
together but I have to go home to
Ponyville and make sure ever Pony there
is safe too I get it go do your thing I
promise Suri I'll find a way to get
Koko's heart back and we'll get revenge
for bulk biceps too you better when you
do find that lunatic let me know there's
a few things I'd like to do to her
myself well then what do you say
Partners only because I look damn good
in a dramatic Alliance
I have the broken heart one piece down
but that's not
enough not yet I Need A Cruel Heart next
one full of
selfishness of malice that shouldn't be
hard to find right I mean this world is
already riddled with
[Music]
evil she would
hate me for this but what else am I
supposed to
do for me to wake up every morning and
forget for half a second that you're
gone this isn't your path I know that's
what you would tell me now and how you
would rather stay gone than to see the
Monster I have become but you aren't
here anymore
one day when we're together again I hope
you can find it within yourself to
forgive me
[Music]
sister only we could back
in wo right where we maybe we'll never
need a reason why wo Dan tell the time
if only we could travel back in time wo
right any
never wo I'm dancing
[Music]
to born from the same branch and leaves
w Wild and
Free living here in harmony don't you
see this is where you want to be when
you leave the world is never what it
seems if only we could travel back in
time wo
right maybe we'll never need a reason
why wo d
until the time if only we could travel
back in time
wo never a Reon